

BENJAMIN SOLT

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

SUMMARY

Full Stack Engineer who is eager to grow and learn new programs.

Prior experience includes 10 years in retail, developing skills in teamwork, communication, and customer service.

Took initiative to self teach Epic Game's Unreal Engine.

SKILLS

- CSS
- HTML
- JavaScript
- 50.70.551.1
- React
- Redux
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Unreal Engine
- 3D Studio Max
- Python
- react Tythe

EDUCATION

LAMBDA SCHOOL - REMOTE

July 2019 - Present Full Stack Web Developer

TEMPLE UNIVERSITY CERTIFICATION IN WEBSITE DESIGN

May 2012

- Intensive course focused on creative web design
- page layouts and art assets
- Utilized HTML, CSS and Dreamweaver

THE ART INSTITUTE OF PHILADELPHIA

December 2007

 Bachelor of Science Degree in Media Arts and Animation

CONTACT INFO

- Bensolt@gmail.com
- Cell: 215 360 5410
- Fort Washington, PA
- Bensolt.com
- <u>LinkedIn</u>
- Github

PROJECTS

PORTFOLIO

April 2020 - Present

Built to showcase personal projects. HTML/CSS | JavaScript | React

 Designed, developed and implemented React based site to display a diverse range of personal projects

GROA - FRONT END DEVELOPER

Feb 17 2020, 8 weeks

Built to recommend movies to user, based on how user rates movies HTML/CSS | JavaScript | React | AWS

- As Front End Developer built Authorization, Login, display layout of movie info
- Solved problems and trouble shot bugs with team members
- Collaborated remotely with team of 6 web developers, 2 data science, and 1 UX designer

REACT-REDUX-APP2

December 2019

Built to demonstrate API call and Redux. HTML/CSS | JavaScript | React? | Halo API

- Implemented Halo API database to visualize data from site
- Built a filter to allow a user to search by name of player

EXPERIENCE

FRESH MARKET - PRODUCE ASSOCIATE

HORSHAM, PA

AUGUST 2016 - JUNE 2019

GIANT GROCERY STORE - PRODUCE ASSOCIATE

WILLOW GROVE, PA NOVEMBER 2013 - AUGUST 2016

- Restock produce and ensure available products are fresh daily
- Respond to shopper inquiries, assist with locating specific products and provide overall friendly customer service